Oh, it's here, it's here.
おー、来た来た
Sasashi-chan, I came to pick you up.
ササシちゃん、迎えに来ちゃったよ
I came to pick you up.
迎えに来ちゃったよ
This is where I came from, all the time.
ここから来てたよね、いつも
It's quite far.
結構遠い
結構遠いね
I was really surprised.
びっくりしたわ、マジで
Hey.
へー
Well, if I go from here, it usually takes about 10 minutes.
じゃ、ここから行ったら、いつも10分くらい来るのにさ、
3. Isn't it going to take 40 minutes?
3、40分かかるんじゃないの?
Ah, it always takes that long.
あ、そんぐらいかかってる、いつも
hey.
ね
I see.
そっか
It's quite far away, isn't it?
結構遠いとこだね、や
Amazing here.
すごいね、ここ
There's SL, I've seen it.
SLがあるよ、見てある
Ah, I see.
あー、そっか
It was my first time, that's for sure.
初めてだった、確かにね
picture?
え?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
this.
これ
What's next to the school?
学校の横に何があるの?
Ah, I see.
あ、そっかそっか
It becomes a daily routine.
日常になっちゃう
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
Because I always watch it.
いつも見てるからや
I don't go to places like this often.
俺、こんなとこ、あんま行かへんからさ
surely.
確かに
I look at it, but I don't go there often.
見てはいるけど、あんま行かないの
Yeah.
うん
I can't go.
行かへんよね
Well, let's go over here, really.
じゃ、こっち行ってみよう、ほんなん
Yeah.
うん
I wonder what's going on.
何があるんやろうね
Yeah.
うん
I've never been there properly either.
私もちゃんと行ったことないから
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I can ride it.
乗れるよ
What, can I ride?
え、乗れるの?
this.
これ
Eh, I want to ride, I want to ride.
え、ちょっと乗りたい、乗りたい
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
行こう、行こう、行こう
Eh, I want to ride.
え、乗りたい
I never ride SL.
SLなんて乗ることない
No, but certainly.
いや、でも確かに
That may be so.
それは、そうかもしれない
Let's go, let's go.
行こう、行こう
I watch it a lot though.
いっぱい見てるけど
That's right.
そうやね
Oh, wow.
え、やば
oh.
おー
Wow, it's serious, well, it really took off.
うわ、本格的っていうか、まあ、ほんまに動いとったんじゃない
of?
の?
Isn't this there?
これ、 そこじゃないの?
Wait, is this really moving?
え、これほんまに動いとったんちゃうの?
this.
これ
Probably, yes.
多分、そう
Eh, then what, um, is this here?
え、じゃあ、ここに何、あの、あれ?
That's where coal is made.
あの、石炭作るところ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだよね
As expected.
やっぱ
Isn't it?
じゃない?
perhaps.
多分
Can I sit here?
ここ、座れるんちゃう?
Try sitting down.
座ってみて
here?
ここ?
Yeah.
うん
Which direction?
どっち向き?
This is it.
これって
Which way is it facing?
どっち向きなの?
Go.
いって
Ah, but it's extremely narrow there.
あ、でもめちゃくちゃ狭いね、そこ
It's small.
狭いよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm riding like this.
こんな、こんなに乗ってるんだ
Yeah.
うん
first time?
初めて?
Yeah.
うん
Because, look.
だって、見て
Look, there's Natsuki's frame next to it.
横にさ、ほら、夏木さんの枠あるよ
This is terrible.
やばいよ
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
If I do this poorly, I'll be found out.
これ、下手したら、バレちゃうね
That's terrible.
やばいね
I get angry.
怒られちゃう
Someone I know is coming.
誰 か知り合い来ちゃうよ
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
Teacher, your position will be stolen.
先生、位置喰らえちゃう
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
やばい、やばい、やばい
Well then, can we go from there?
え、 じゃあ、あっちから行けるのかな?
Is this the only place you can go?
こっちしか行けないの?
Ah, I can get off here.
あ、こっち降りれる
Oh, I can get off.
あ、降りれるんだ
Ah, nice here.
あ、いいね、ここ
nice.
いいね
That's nice, that's, uh, amazing.
いいね、なんか、あの、すごいね、
this.
これ
Something like this, a railroad...
なんか、あの、こういうね、 鉄道が、
I loved it a long time ago.
結構昔好きやったからさ
oh yeah.
そうそう
I really love this kind of thing.
こういうの、すごい愛好きなのよ
I like boys.
男の子好きなもんです
oh yeah.
そうそう
Yeah?
うん?
nice.
いいね
Neighboring school.
隣学校
What was it?
何だった?
It's the school next door.
隣学校なの
I know.
知ってる
I know it's crazy.
知ってるやばい
I know, I know.
知ってる知ってる
I know because I went to pick her up earlier.
さっき、迎えに行ったから、知ってる
surely.
確かに
Hey, hey, hey, hey
ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょっと、
what?
何?
Please raise it a little higher.
少し上に上げてください
Please raise it a little more.
もう 少し上げてください
So cute.
とてもかわいい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I love being shy.
恥ずかしがっているのは大好物です
There's no point in doing anything.
何をしても無駄です
No matter what you do, it's not in vain.
何をしても無駄ではありません
Looks embarrassing.
恥ずかしそう
Someone might come.
人が来るかもしれません
Please spread your legs a little more.
もう少し足を広げてください
If the people at school find out, it's over.
学校の人たちにバレたら終わりです
What?
なんて?
If the people at school find out, it's over.
学校の人たちにバレたら終わりです
It's over.
終わりです
That's certainly true.
それは確かにそうです
I don't like it.
嫌だね
Oh, I heard a beep.
あ、ピー音が鳴りました
There was a beep.
ピー音が鳴りました
Will you get angry?
怒られる?
I get angry.
怒られる
There would be a lot of people here.
ここだったら人がいっぱいやんか
There's a lot of people there.
人がいっぱいやんか
That old lady is beeping at me.
あのおでさん、俺を向かってピーしてるんだけど
Can I touch you in the SL over there?
あ そこのSLの中で、 ちょっと触っていい?
transformation.
変態
It's a pervert.
変態です
The teacher is a pervert.
先生は変態なんです
After looking at that white bread, I touched it and felt how moist it was now.
あの白パンを見てしまったら、 今のしっとりした感じを 触って
Once it's done, I can't help but want to touch it.
しま ったら、 ちょっと触りたくて仕方がない
It's raining too.
雨も降ってきたし
That's true.
それはある
It's SL Square at SL Square.
SL広場のSL広場じゃん
It's not SL Square.
SL広場じゃない
Let's indulge in SL meta.
SLメタで甘えどりしようか
That's right.
そうね
Let's do that.
そうしよう
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
It's raining.
雨降ってきてるし
I have to go quickly.
早く行かなきゃ
Because there are quite a few people.
結構人いるからな
Ah, it's really good.
あ、やっぱりいいね
I have that one though.
そっちいるけどさ
There's meta-meta.
メタメタいる
I'll have you come over for a while.
ちょっと 来てもらうわけですよ
Oh my gosh, that's erotic.
あ、やば、エロ
I was surprised, but it worked.
びっくりしたんだけど、手がする
You're pushing right in.
突っ込んでるね
I had a skirt potion.
スカートポーションしてた
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
She's wearing such naughty pants.
こんなエッチなパンツしてる
Really.
ほんまに
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's refreshing after all.
やっぱりしっぱりしてるわ
It might be dangerous.
やばいかも
There's so many people gathered there.
すっごいそこに集まってる
people in exercise.
運動の人たち
I might not be able to see it.
見えないかも
見 えないかも
I might not be able to become one.
なれないかも
Erotic.
エロ
Shift.
ずらせ
Ah, that's erotic.
あ、エロい
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
Oh no.
やば
It's such a beautiful color.
めっちゃ綺麗な色してる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
cute.
かわいい
Next door.
隣で
How about going to the place you go to next door?
通ってるところを隣でするのってどう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I don't know.
わかんない
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
Because I can't see it.
見えないから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
I can't see it.
見えないって
terrible.
やばい
I get excited.
テンション上がる
Oh no, seriously.
やばい、マジで
Oh no.
やば
Not really.
ほんとない
This village.
この 村は
difficult.
難しい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so messed up.
めっちゃくちゃくちゃ
Go right in.
すっと入る
slimy.
ぬるぬる
I'm a bit against it.
反対やんか、ちょっと
Natsuki-chan, you're a pervert.
なつきちゃん、変態やね
Erotic.
エロい
Biccha bicha.
びっちゃびちゃ
Go right in.
すっと入る
I went straight in.
すっと入った
Messed up.
くちゃくちゃ
It's okay.
無 事だね
Do you understand?
わかる?
Soaked.
びちゃびちゃ
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
I wish I had done this.
こんなんしてたらさ
Was it cold?
寒かった?
No?
ダメ?
I want to put it away though.
しまいたいけど
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
You'll find out.
バレちゃうね
If I find out, I'll be expelled from school.
バ レたら退学しちゃうね
Oh no, seriously.
や ばい、マジで
Before you lick it.
舐める前にさ
This is amazing.
すっごいこれ
Show your butt to this side?
お尻、こっち側に見せる?
A little while ago.
もうちょっと前に
Wow, erotic.
うわ、エロ
I felt sick.
気持ち悪くなった
Yocchi-san, you're really stiff.
よっちさん、 めっちゃ固いわ
Being embarrassed and feeling different.
恥ずかしいのと気持ちの違う
strong.
強 い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Being embarrassed is stronger.
恥ずかしいほうが強い
I can't stand it.
たまらん
But I seriously can't stand it.
でもマジたまらんわ
Can I have you lick me?
舐めてもらっていい?
So cute.
かわいいな
Let's sleep.
寝こう
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Look.
見て
Shiny.
テカテカ
what?
なに?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいわ
Biccha bicha.
びっちゃびちゃ
Take it off.
外して
It's insanely big.
めちゃくちゃ大きい
め ちゃくちゃ大きい
Well then, below.
じゃあ、下
Below, Chill-chan.
下、チルちゃん
Down, down, Chill-chan.
下、下、チルちゃん
Down.
下
Above, Chill-chan.
上、チルちゃん
superior.
上
Above, Chill-chan.
上、チルちゃん
top, chi
上、チ
Lu-chan.
ル ちゃん
Above, Chill-chan.
上、チルちゃん
For this one.
こっち向け
This one is good too.
こっちもいい
Yeah.
うん
This one is good too.
こっちもいい
ben
ベン
Please create the .
ジ を生み出してください
I came two weeks ago.
私は2週間前に来ました
I'm very happy.
とても嬉しいです
I played with Reiki-chan.
レ イ キ ちゃんと一緒に遊びました
I remembered that we rested until 9 o'clock at 11 o'clock.
私たちは11時の9時まで休んだことを思い出しました
Everyone's fight was bad.
みんなの争いが悪かったです
what happened?
どうしたの?
Haven't you seen it?
見 ない?
Did you see it?
見えた?
I don't want to see it.
見えたくない
thank you.
ありがとう
I really don't care.
めっちゃ気にしない
thank you.
ありがとう
end?
終わり?
Is it over?
終わりなの?
picture?
え?
Is it okay?
いいの?
still?
まだ?
Actually, I actually wanted to put it inside Natsuki-chan, but...
実はさ、 本当は、なつきちゃんの中に入れたかったんだけど、
But, as expected, I don't think it's possible right now.
でも さすがに、 今はダメかなって思って
I've given up, but when people say cute things like that,
諦めてるけど、 そんな可愛いこと言われるによったら、
I'll go, then.
行 っちゃうよ、じゃあ
Is it okay?
いいの?
real?
ほんと?
Then let's go.
じゃあ行こうか
It's really cute though.
めっちゃ可愛いねんけど
I also do high speed rolls.
高速ロールもやる
Use a sense of distance.
距離感使う
Stretch it out.
伸ばして
expensive?
高い?
Is it expensive?
高いの?
expensive.
高い
It wasn't delicious.
美味しくはなかった
美味 しくはなかった
He says he's taking classes with the teacher, so he doesn't think about that.
先生の授業受けてると言うから、そんなこと考えてない
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
ちょっと ね
I always wear my uniform, so I'm in class.
制服いつも着てるから、授業中
Because I think it's so accurate.
こんなにちゃんとあると思うから
Well.
まあね
Because it looks small.
小さく見えるからね
It's painful though.
辛いけど
I really like it.
めっちゃいっちいした気が入ってる
Did you wear this much during class?
授業中にこんなに履いてたの?
everytime?
いつも?
Did you always wear it like this?
いつもこんなに履いてたの?
Try looking for it earlier.
さっきの時、探してみて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Is it easier to line up than before?
さっきより並みやすい?
Yeah.
うん
I went right away after putting it in.
入れてすぐ行っちゃったよ
I was looking outside.
外見てた
what?
なに?
why?
なぜ?
It's like we did it together outside.
外 で一緒やったしさ
We did it together for the first time.
初めては一緒やった
What should I do?
どうする?
What do you want to do?
どうしたい?
Teacher, teacher, I was listening.
先生、先生聞いてた
Will you be with me a little longer?
もうちょっと一緒にいる?
Will you be there forever?
ずっといる?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Teacher, pervert.
先生、変態
He's a pervert.
変態だよ
Because I think I'm attractive.
自分が魅力的だと思うから
Is it my fault?
私のせいか
I almost miss it.
ほぼ懐けちゃう
People who want to be complete.
完全にしたい人
I agree.
そうだね
From my mother.
お母さんのかより
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sensei, I just said most of the last thing.
先生、さっき、 最後ほとんど話しちゃったよ
what?
何?
What should I do?
どうすればいい?
I want all the undercoat removed.
下毛だけ全部取ってほしい
I see.
なるほどね
Take a quick look once.
一 回、軽く見て
Remove only the undercoat.
下毛だけ取って
yes.
そう
what?
何?
Don't need a mask?
マスクはいらない?
There isn't.
ないぞ
Something is coming out.
何か出てきてるよ
Yes, I'm fine.
そう、元気
I'm fine, I'm fine.
元気、元気